burrellesluce.com 2016-11-25

# Site Privacy Policy | BurrellesLuce

## At Burrelles _Luce_ , we understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.

This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Burrelles _Luce_ (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

"Personally Identifiable Information" refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, company name address, phone number, fax number, email address. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

### What personally identifiable information is collected?

We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature of the service that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase.

### How does the site use personally identifiable information?

We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying requests on the Site. We may phone or e-mail Visitors and Authorized Customers about our services or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

### With whom may the information may be shared?

We do not reveal any Personally Identifiable Information that we collect about you, your use of the Services or any information that you post on your Site to anyone else.

### How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Burrelles _Luce_ is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or unauthorized employees of Burrelles _Luce_.

### What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?

Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at [info@burrellesLuce.com](mailto:info@burrellesLuce.com)

### Are Cookies used on the Site?

Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select.

### How is login information used on the Site?

Burrelles _Luce_ uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

### How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?

All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.

### How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?

Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at [info@burrellesLuce.com](mailto:info@burrellesLuce.com)

### Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?

We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting [info@burrellesluce.com](mailto:info@burrellesLuce.com). However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that inpidual in any way moving forward.

### What happens if the Privacy Policy changes?

We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.

### Links:

This web site may contain links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
